<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on My test case for documentat.io</title>
    <link>http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on My test case for documentat.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to enable HTTPS on your site with Apache using Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/docs/guide-lets-encrypt-for-apache-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/docs/guide-lets-encrypt-for-apache-en/</guid>
      <description>How to enable HTTPS on your site with Apache using Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt #  Let’s Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority (CA), run for the public’s benefit. It is a service provided by the Internet Security Research Group (ISRG). The process of obtaining certificates is simplified due to the presence of the Certbot ACME client, which automates almost all the necessary operations, including for Apache.
Despite the fact that the SSL-certificates Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt free, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that the level of encryption is lower than that of paid certificates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to enable HTTPS on your site with nginx using Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/docs/guide-lets-encrypt-for-nginx-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sashainthewild.github.io/en/docs/guide-lets-encrypt-for-nginx-en/</guid>
      <description>How to enable HTTPS on your site with nginx using Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt #  Let’s Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority (CA), run for the public’s benefit. It is a service provided by the Internet Security Research Group (ISRG). The process of obtaining certificates is simplified due to the presence of the Certbot ACME client, which automates almost all the necessary operations.
Despite the fact that the SSL-certificates Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt free, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that the level of encryption is lower than that of paid certificates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
